Previously on Dating Alys Perez.
Cristine and I aren't the same size.
Are you calling yourself fat?
Excuse me?!
Ms. Alys, the gown might get damaged!
Shut up!
On the count of three,
you're gonna zip it up.
No matter what happens,
even if it gets torn, I don’t care!
You and Tripp,
good together.
You and Drake,
epic!
Can you feel that, Alys?
God, it's so pretty!
You'll drop dead when
you see Alys in this!
She's always beautiful.
That's the heartbeat of a man
who's obsessed with you.
When's the proposal?
Proposal?
The day before the wedding.
Now it's up to Alys.
If she'll say yes.
She will.
Tripp.
Hey, Silly!
Hey.
What happened?
Why are you crying?
Hold on.
Let me get you some water.
Wait, Zy.
Feel better?
Tell me.
What's wrong?
I'm sorry.
Sorry for what?
What's the matter?
Please don't be mad.
Is this about Drake again?
But please,
listen to me first.
Okay?
I...
I overheard
him say...
that he's proposing to me.
Huh?!
What?!
Marco, please calm down!
Listen to me first, please?
Do you remember...
Do you remember
Cristine and Drake's wedding?
It turns out it was meant for us.
I'm sorry, I really didn't know!
Marco —
Motherfucker!
I'll kill him!
I'll kill that shit!
Marco, please...
Marco, please, Marco...
Zy!
Stop it!
Don't touch me!
Damn it!
Please, Marco, calm down.
Don't get mad.
- You know I would never—
- Don't get mad?!
Don't get mad, Zy?!
Just think for a second!
How can I not be angry?!
He wants to propose to my girlfriend!
My girlfriend, Zy!
My girlfriend!
That shit wants to marry her!
What do you expect me to do?
Celebrate?
Come on, think!
Marco, I would never
accept his proposal.
You know that you're
the only one I love.
I know you love me, Zy.
You always say that.
But tell me the truth.
Am I really the only one you love?
Answer me!
Is it just me?
Of course, Tripp!
Why would you ask me that?
You're the only one I love.
Then, why?
No matter how many
times you say it,
I can still feel something’s off.
Like...
why do I still feel like
I’m just a rebound?
The moment Drake shows up,
that’ll be it.
You'll just throw me away!
Tripp, please!
I'm right, aren't I?
I don't know why I'm like this, Zy.
I know...
what we have will never compare
to what you and Drake have.
Do you know why?
What am I, anyway?
I'm just a rebound!
Forced!
We forced ourselves together.
Us.
There was never an us!
Tripp, don't say that!
We're nothing!
Don't say that, Tripp, please!
I was after you...
for two years, Zy!
Two years.
It was all hard work, all genuine!
All for nothing!
Nothing I do will ever compare
to what you and Drake have.
I know that!
I’m such an idiot!
If I never cared about you,
then I would have married
Drake a long time ago.
But I'm here, aren't I?
I am with you, Tripp.
I'm here with you.
I'm trying to fix this.
What else do I have to do?!
It hurts.
But you know what really hurts?
What I feel right now.
You know what really hurts?
The fact that I could do everything,
and none of it will matter.
None of it will matter
because I came late!
What do I have to do
to prove to you that I love you?
And you're the only one I love!
Marry me.
Marry me and I'll be at peace.
That's it.
That's all I need.
So?
That's all.
Tripp...
There it is!
That's it!
That's where we always end up.
With Drake!
It will always be Drake!
I knew it!
Tripp, enough with Drake,
I'm here!
I am trying to fix this.
But you keep going back to Drake.
Let's fix this, please!
I'm trying to explain myself,
- but you're being a fucking asshole!
- I’m done!
An asshole?
God, what's happening?
Where is the Tripp I know?
The Tripp that's always calm?
Four years!
Four fucking years!
I let myself be a fool for you!
Haven't I earned a
moment to be the asshole?
Just this once!
Get out of here.
Please, I'm begging you.
- No.
- Just leave.
I don't want to.
We’ll just end up fighting, Zy.
Leave!
- Please, Tripp, I'm sorry.
- Please, please!
- Please!
- Please, Tripp, I'm sorry.
Leave!
I don't want to!
Just leave.
Leave!
You threw it all away!
Fuck!
Drake.
Just stop this already, will you?
I'm so tired of this.
You're making this hard for me.
What?
All of this.
Stop it.
The chasing.
The begging.
The hurting.
Just stop it.
What if I don't want to, Alys?
Drake, please.
Please!
Enough, please.
Alys, I don't believe you.
Drake,
if you still love me,
stop it, please.
Please.
I wish I could.
But I can't, Alys.
I don't want to.
Enough.
Enough!
Stop begging me, Drake!
Even if you cry, beg
and kneel before me,
there’s nothing left I can give you.
Nothing!
I've given it all to Tripp!
Do you think I wanted this?!
Alys!
Do you think I enjoy being a fool?!
No, Alys!
You're tired?!
Fine.
I hurt you.
Sure.
But Alys, even just once,
did you ever ask me how I was?
You have no idea
what I've been through, Alys.
You know nothing.
I left you, that's true.
Alys, those moments haunt me
every single night.
Every fucking night, I wanted to
fly to New York and apologize to you.
But you don't know anything.
Who am I, anyway, Alys?
Right?
Do you know how much I cried
when I found out about you and Tripp?
Even my dad hated you, Alys.
It was always about you.
What about me?
And yes,
call me pathetic, Alys.
I had no one, then.
You had Tripp and Tofer.
It's not fair.
You were so unfair, Alys.
You spent years hating me.
While I spent years wishing
you'd come back to me.
Fine, call me pathetic.
I don't know anymore.
I'm so confused, Drake.
Please.
Please stop this.
Alys.
The wedding is in two days.
You can marry me
or lose me forever.
For the last time,
I'll be pathetic.
Aww, baby.
What happened?
It really hurts, Mommy.
Is this about the cousins?
I don’t want to hurt them, Mommy.
Oh.
I know, baby.
You can't escape the pain,
by avoiding to make a decision.
The days just kept getting longer.
Baby,
you have to ask yourself.
What if
you lose both of them?
Who would be the
first person you'd look for?
Who is the one
you could never let go of?
Alys.
Alys, get up.
Get up!
What?
Tripp and Drake are downstairs.
What?!
Get up!
Should I face them or not?
I just finished crying,
and now this again?
Can't I get a time out and rest?
My heart hurts so much.
- Alys.
You two, just stop already!
Would you let me rest?
Tripp?
What happened to you?
I'm protecting what's mine.
Drake, what did you —
Drake...
I'm just wondering
how it would feel
seeing you take care of him.
Alys, we're both hurt.
I thought this would hurt more.
But, Alys I feel nothing.
You've made me numb.
- Drake...
- Alys!
Don't.
Please.
Stay with me.
Please!
Tripp, come on.
Just this once.
Show him that I’m your priority.
Please!
All my life, Zy.
I always come second.
Please!
Just this once,
let my feelings come first.
Tripp.
You know, I always put you first.
Just this once, please.
I need to speak to Drake.
Alys,
I know you love me.
But I know you still love Drake.
And I'm okay with you loving us both.
There's only one thing I ask of you.
Love me a little more.
Just a little.
Please, Zy.
I'm begging you.
Please.
I can't do this anymore.
I give up.
Forget about the wedding, Alys.
Nanny, thank you.
Nanny!
Yes, Ma'am?
Where's Mom?
She hasn't arrived yet.
Okay, thank you!
Hello?
Mom,
where are you?
I'm buying a dress for tomorrow.
And gifts for you and your husband.
Mom, you know the wedding is fake.
Why are you acting like it's real?
Why?
Can't I attend my daughter's wedding?
Mom, the wedding's not real!
It was just a ploy by me and Drake.
Wait.
Speaking of...
he hasn't even texted me yet.
I haven't been able to reach him.
Well, I'm still hoping it's true.
I'm doing a fitting now. Bye!
But —
Annoying.
I'm done.
All I want to do is relax.
Who’s this?
Hello?
Cristine!
What's up, honey?
Fier, you bitch!
Where exactly are you
here in the Philippines?
Oh my god!
You're here in the Philippines already?
Obviously, honey!
I'll go to your house tomorrow, okay?
My brothers ditched me.
Oh god.
The twins haven't changed.
Still as stubborn as ever.
I know, right?
Oh no, Fier.
I have plans tomorrow.
Can we just reschedule or something?
Hmm... where?
What if I come with you?
There's no one in the
house but the maids.
And then Chance and Lourd
are out picking up girls. My god!
Fine. Okay.
But we're going to a
wedding tomorrow, okay?
No naughty business.
Me?
Naughty?
Remember when you attended
your long-time crush's wedding
and you were wearing a black dress?
Fier, you're my plus one.
Remember!
Fine, whatever.
You know what? Fine.
I'll see you.
I'll go to sleep, so I'll be
pretty when you see me.
Okay? Goodnight.
Goodnight!
See you!
Bye bye!
Good morning, brat!
Mom, what is going on?
If you just followed what I said,
then Drake would be
my son-in-law by now!
Mom, if you want Drake that badly...
Go! Ask him to marry you instead.
Aren't you gonna get ready?
It's your wedding.
Mom, come on.
I'm the only one going.
You're not coming with me!
Cristine, Fier's here.
What a pretty girl!
Oh, how come you didn't end up
being that pretty?
Well,
because I'm just like you.
Such a brat!
Go see your friend.
Okay.
Fier!
Coming!
Who's getting married, anyway?
Drake.
Drake who?
Drake Palma.
Mmm! Sounds yummy.
Fier!
The person is getting married.
Would you avoid having dirty thoughts?
If I know you,
you like him.
And you're sad
because he's marrying someone else.
Yuck!
Can I puke right now?
My god!
That's disgusting, Fier.
Drake and I aren't together, okay?
In my nightmares
maybe it could happen.
Tell me the truth, honey.
I know you!
Well then, I guess you
don't know me well enough!
Come on, tell me the truth, honey.
- I swear—
- Whatever, let's go.
Marry me...
or lose me forever.
I know you're coming.
Please, Alys.
What are you doing, Alys?
You should know what
you’re supposed to do.
You know it better than anyone.
Drake!
Drake,
what happened?
Why is there no one at the church?
Cristine...
My god, Drake...
What happened?!
You had me worried!
No one heard anything from you!
To Uncle Steve, not even an update.
Please don't yell at me.
I've been yelled at too
many times since last week.
Drake, please.
Just stop.
Let's go home.
Drake, please.
Forget about Alys.
Please!
Stop this game.
Look, mister.
Your bride ditched you.
Move on!
Fier!
What?
I'm just saying the truth here.
She left him!
Move on, dude!
The world won't stop spinning
just because she left.
Fier, you don't know
anything about them.
Please!
Stop bitching!
Dear god!
Look, mister!
I don't know you,
so I can only give
an outsider's opinion.
And from how I see it?
She doesn't care.
I hate it when people beg for
something that they can't have.
You know, if you want it bad enough,
make it happen!
- Begging will only make you look path—
- Shut up.
Drake!
She's so gonna regret
letting him down.
Could you give me
Mr. Grumpy's number?
What?
His number.
Hello?
The guy's heartbroken!
So?
He's single now.
My God.
Make sure the documents are all there.
Yes, sir.
Okay.
Alys?
Alys!
- Uncle Tristan!
- How are you?
- Where’s Tripp?
What?
Tripp?
Yes, Uncle.
Where is he?
We haven't spoken for over a week.
Oh my god, I didn't know!
He's already in New York!
Since last Tuesday.
I thought he told you.
New York?
Yes.
Our projects started picking up.
I didn't know that
he'd take on all of them.
He'll be busy for a month!
One month?!
Yeah, one month.
I'm really sorry, Alys.
How about this?
If you want, I can give you the number
of the hotel he's staying at.
No, that's okay, Uncle.
Thank you.
What? Are you sure?
Yes, Uncle. No, thank you.
Okay, you just take care.
I'll see you around.
- Take care, Uncle.
- Okay, I have to go. Bye.
Tripp...
Please pick up.
Your call has been forwarded
to an automatic voice message system.
At the tone, please record your message.
Tripp...
Can we stop fighting?
Drake gave up. Didn't you see that?
Please don't be like this.
Why are you being like this?
Was I just a trophy to you?
Did you only love me
because Drake loved me?
And now that he's left me,
you're leaving me too?
Tripp please, don't be like this.
Alys!
What?
Hey, are you okay?
I’m worried about you.
Even if it isn't obvious.
What do you want, Tofer?
Well...
Uncle Tristan said Tripp wasn't home.
So I thought I'd bother you instead.
Then go follow him in New York!
Hey.
Why are you even here?
Don't be so mean.
Don't blame Marco's faults on me.
Don't you remember?
We're Best Friends Forever, right?
But Alys,
believe me...
I get you.
I know how it feels.
I know what you're going through.
BFF?
Sorry for being moody, Tofer.
Come on!
Like I said,
I get you.
So, you want to grab some dinner?
G! Let's go!
Hurry up! Get on your feet!
You're so slow. Take a bath!
Let's go. Hurry!
So?
Where are we going?
Where do you want to go?
I'm asking you because it's your call.
Alright, fine. How about this?
We grab an early dinner,
and then we party after.
So, are you game?
You know me, Tofer.
I go with the flow.
Then, let's go!
Are you having fun, Alys?!
Come on, let's have some drinks!
Come on, let's go!
I need to get something from the car.
What is it now?
Fine, I'll go with you.
Oh no, no. It's fine.
I can do it myself.
I'll just find you later, okay?
Fine.
Here.
Take good care of my car, okay?
- If something happens to it...
- Thanks for the concern...
I love that car more than you!
Let's go?
My god!
Drake, I'm really sorry.
Fier, why did I bring you again?
Shut up, Cristine!
You know, Drake doesn't mind,
but all you do is complain!
What do you mean he doesn't mind?
Look at his brows, okay?
They're gonna cramp from
furrowing because of you.
You know what, Cristine?
If you're just gonna
nag the whole night,
why don't you go home?
I'll manage Drake.
No, no, Fier.
You wish. Okay?
I'm just afraid of what you
might do to my friend.
Why'd you stop walking?
Who is she?
Hi, Alys!
Hello.
Oh!
So, you're Alys.
Oh, well,
I think I should thank you!
What are you talking about?
Thanks for breaking this man's heart.
I'm here to collect the pieces.
Who are you?
Marie...
Fier...
Sandoval,
darling.
No, no, no.
Sorry, Alys.
That's the way she always is.
Please don't be offended.
None taken.
Alright.
Maybe you’re going somewhere
with Ms. Marie Fier Sandoval.
Yeah.
Let's go now.
Remember my name.
Let's go, Drake.
Bitch!
I have a place. You game?
Oh, but... because...
Alys!
I've been looking for you!
Where did you go?
You know I’m a girl magnet, right?
My god, Alys!
I thought you left me.
I’m sorry, it took so long.
I needed to get some air.
Uhm...
Hi!
What's her problem?
- What?!
Let's go, let's go grab some drinks!
Woo, let's go!
Here we go.
Let's have some drinks!
Here! Have a shot!
I’ll have some later.
Well then, more shots for me!
How boring!
Really? We're just gonna
sit out the entire night?
We're not just sitting!
We're drinking too.
Right, Drake?
Let’s dance.
Please!
I'll kiss you if you don't.
You don't believe me?
Dare?
Oh my god, Fier!
Drake!
Come here!
Here!
Sit here!
What?!
Why did you do that?
No reason.
Cristine, why are you mad?
It's not like I killed him or anything!
He's very much alive!
Come on, Cristine!
You know,
he's old enough.
He’s single
and he’s hot!
Let the man have a life!
Have a drink.
Come on.
Just relax.
If you really weren't my friend.
Let’s go, dance with me.
Excuse me, excuse me.
Let's dance!
Loosen up, Drake!
Don't you know how to dance?
Stop it.
Come on, take a shot!
It's your turn!
What’s up?
Fine, I'll show you.
There you go!
Come on, let's take the stage.
Excuse me, guys.
Let’s go, come on.
Come on! Loosen up, Drake!
Guys, do you wanna see him dance?!
- Yeah!
- Go!
I swear, I’ll volunteer you to
a body shot if you don’t dance.
Pervert.
It’s fun.
- Go!
There’s that sexy smile.
Come on.
Game.
Drake's dancing.
He never danced with me
like that before.
Can I have a shot?
That’s your shot.
Oh.
Hey, Perez, slow down!
Perez, Perez, that's enough!
Here. Take a lemon, first.
I need something stronger.
Jeez, Perez!
Do you wanna drink
yourself to the hospital?!
You're gonna get alcohol poisoning!
Can you just relax, Tofer?
I'm going to stop
when I want to stop.
Stop when I want to stop?
What?
You’re drinking the whole bottle?!
That's enough, Perez! Stop it!
You're no drunk.
Will you stop?!
Fine, I'll put it in a glass.
You happy?
Bottoms up!
You have some nerve.
You weren't satisfied with just
proposing to my girlfriend.
You really went all the way
to her house?
Drake...
It's been fucking years!
Just move on like everybody else!
For fuck's sake!
Alys and I are happy!
Just leave us alone!
Are you sure Alys
is happy with you?
Would you like to know
how she looks at me
even when she's mad at me?
I can feel how much she still loves me.
You fucking asshole.
I don't know why I'm the
only one who can see it.
You're the asshole.
Weren't you the reason why
we broke up in New York?
No.
No, it’s not.
You broke up because you left her.
And you saved her?
What an amazing plan.
You manipulated everything.
Me,
Alys,
and the situation.
All just to steal Alys.
If I'm an asshole then you're worse.
Why do you steal everything from me?!
You stole her!
Hey, you two!
Get in!
I'll call Alys.
You both look like idiots.
I can't do this anymore.
I give up.
Forget about the wedding, Alys.
I'm sorry, Alys.
Seeing you in pain breaks me.
This is for you.
I want you to be happy without me.
For now.
On the next episode of
Dating Alys Perez.
I have great news!
What is it?
Tripp is back!
Alys!
Kei?!
You little witch!
Let's go, Fier.
Have you seen Tripp?
Did you have a fight?
We can't be together!
There is no us! Are you dumb?
Who is Fier?
Goodbye, Alys.
Drake...
I thought it was just time off.
We never broke up, did we?
Okay, Alys.
Let's break up.
I'm setting you free.
Set me free, too.